(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
なんであなたにはできないの
Why can't you do it?
なんてさ 陰口言われたり 呆れられたり
They say things like that, badmouthing me and giving up on me.
口角下がるってばいて
I said my mouth corners are drooping, ouch.
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
And the train leaves me behind.
葉物野菜もスピード速すぎだね
Leafy greens spoil way too fast, don't they?
ありのままの素敵さだけじゃ足りないんだ
Just being wonderful as I am isn't enough.
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっとここまで連れてきたんだ
I worked myself to death every day to finally bring us this far.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand.
分かってほしくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
My hardships, too...
食い物かご存知ないで
Don't you realize they're just fodder?
いてね
Just stay there.
きっとあなたにもできるはず
"You can surely do it too," they say.
なんてさ 言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be as irresponsible as those words imply.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って賭ける値打ちはあると思った
Still, I thought it was worth betting my life and working hard for.
投げ出したくなるよ
It makes me want to throw it all away.
でも諦めたくはない
But I don't want to give up.
私の未来も
My future, too.
失敗も全部私だけのもの
My failures, all of it, belong only to me.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand.
分かってほしくない
I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も
My hardships, too...
食い物かご存知ないで
Don't you realize they're just fodder?
投げ出したくなるよ
I want to throw it all away.
でも諦めたくはない
But I don't want to give up.
私の未来も
My future, too.
失敗も全部渡さないよ
I won't hand over my failures, either.
気付かない 気付かないでいて
Don't notice, please don't notice.
可愛いだけの私でいい
Just "cute me" is fine.
愛す痛みにトロけて分かんなくなる
Melting in the sweet pain of love, I lose myself.
夢も愛もキュッとして いっぱいだから持ちきれない
Holding dreams and love tight, it's too much to carry.
でも欲張りすぎて 独り占めしていく
But I'm too greedy, so I'll keep it all to myself.
もうラクラクちゅーちゅー 恋に落ちちゃって
I'm already falling head over heels in love, chu-chu.
戻れない
I can't go back.
あれあれなんで ふわりと心がまだ熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my heart still gently heat up?
ラクラクちゅーちゅー 君の重力で 引き寄せて
Easy-peasy chu-chu, pull me close with your gravity.
カレイドスコープ 覗いてるみたいで
It's like looking into a kaleidoscope.
キラキラな未来見たい 分からない
I want to see a sparkling future, I don't know.
青 アップ＆ダウンで 感情振り回す
Blue, up and down, swaying my emotions.
You and 今日は 私 四六時中
You and today, I'm thinking of you 24/7.
カレンダー30日 でも足りない
Even 30 days in a calendar isn't enough.
あれもこれもそれも 全部したい
That, this, and that too, I want to do it all.
無限大の愛だけど 失敗
It's infinite love, but a failure.
だけど諦めない
But I won't give up.
まだ欲張りだから 君としていく
I'm still greedy, so I'll keep going with you.
もうラクラクちゅーちゅー 心がハマって
Already easy-peasy chu-chu, my heart is hooked.
抜け出せない
I can't escape.
あれあれなんで 目まぐるしい心がまだ熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my dizzying heart still heat up?
ラクラクちゅーちゅー スピード重視で 引き寄せて
Easy-peasy chu-chu, focusing on speed, pull me close.
カレイドスコープ 覗いてるみたいで
It's like looking into a kaleidoscope.
キラキラな未来見たい 分からない
I want to see a sparkling future, I don't know.
バーチャル？リアル？どっちかわいい？
Virtual? Real? Which is cuter?
バーチャル？リアル？どっちカワイイ？
バーチャル？リアル？どっち可愛い？
Virtual? Real? Which is cuter?
バーチャル！リアル！どっちもKawaii♡
Virtual! Real! Both are Kawaii♡
Check it ちゅきちゅき ちゅるっChu チェリチェリー チューインチュイン
Check it, chuki chuki churu-Chu, cherry cherry, chuin chuin.
Check it ちゅきちゅき ちゅるっChu チェリチェリー チューインチュイン ちょ
Check it, chuki chuki churu-Chu, cherry cherry, chuin chuin, cho.
サムネタップ はじめましてきゅんきゅん♡ってしたなら
Thumbnail tap, if you felt a 'kyun-kyun'♡ when we first met...
ハート押して通知はON いつでもCome on
Press the heart, turn notifications ON, Come on anytime.
一緒に踊ろうよ On and on
Let's dance together, On and on.
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I want to eat snacks but I'm on a diet.
キミの好みにアップデート中
Updating to your preferences right now.
ポチり更新 キミと交信
Click to refresh, communicating with you.
もっと推してほしいの♡
I want you to support me more♡
「バーチャル？リアル？どっちが好き？」
"Virtual? Real? Which do you like?"
繋がる1 2 3 次元
Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions.
ワントゥースリーで飛び越えて
Jumping over with a one-two-three.
今やネットもリアルです
Now the internet is also real.
チクチクしないでラブとピースで
Don't be prickly, with love and peace.
ときめいちゃう 時かけGIRL
A heart-thumping, time-traveling GIRL.
混ぜれば 最強 バチャリアラブ♡
Mix them and it's the strongest, Virtual Real Love♡
Check it ちゅきちゅき ちゅるっChu チェリチェリー チューインチュイン
Check it, chuki chuki churu-Chu, cherry cherry, chuin chuin.
Check it ちゅきちゅき ちゅるっChu チェリチェリー チューインチュイン ちょ
Check it, chuki chuki churu-Chu, cherry cherry, chuin chuin, cho.
2番にスワイプ Beat足してきゅんきゅん♡ってしたなら
Swipe to the 2nd verse, if you felt 'kyun-kyun'♡ with the added beat...
手叩いてガチ勢も エンジョイ勢も
Clap your hands, both hardcore fans and casual fans.
一緒に踊ろうよ On and on
Let's dance together, On and on.
界隈ちがうけど コラボ中
Different communities, but we're collaborating.
New楽しいこと リサーチ中
Researching new fun things right now.
ぴぴぴテレパシー 今日も配信
Pipipi telepathy, streaming today too.
もっとハート欲しいの♡
I want more hearts♡
ねぇ ねぇ どっちかわいい？
Hey, hey, which is cuter?
どっちかわいい？どっちかわいい？
Which is cuter? Which is cuter?
ねぇ ねぇ どっちかわいい？
Hey, hey, which is cuter?
どっちかわいい？どっちかわいい？
Which is cuter? Which is cuter?
どっちもKawaii♡
Both are Kawaii♡
1 2 3 次元
1, 2, 3 Dimensions.
One Two Three で飛び越えて
Jumping over with a One, Two, Three.
今やネット盛り上がるです
Now we're getting hyped on the net.
チクチクしないで Love & Peace
Don't be prickly, Love & Peace.
チクタク ワワワ
Tick-tock wa wa wa.
トキメキチャウ
My heart is pounding.
トキカケガール
Time-leaping Girl.
2D 3D Real World
混ぜれば最強...
Mix them and it's the strongest...
僕らが見ている太陽は
The sun we are looking at,
8分前の姿で
is its form from 8 minutes ago.
実はちょっと昔らしい
Actually, it seems it's a bit in the past.
そう考えると不思議かもね
Thinking about it, it's kind of mysterious.
そこにあるようでいて
It seems to be there,
少しずれた時間を過ごしてる
but we're spending time slightly shifted.
きっと僕らの...
Surely our...
アマテラス テラス この手で
Amaterasu, illuminate with these hands,
触れて 笑って 踊りましょう
touch, laugh, and let's dance.
アマテラス テラス 聞かせて
Amaterasu, illuminate, let me hear,
あのね 君だって 歌えるよ
you know, even you can sing it.
誰にだって 降り注いだ
It poured down on everyone,
8分前の光が指す方へ
towards where the light from 8 minutes ago points.
僕らは分かり合えない
We cannot understand each other.
お互いの世界には
In each other's worlds,
誰も価値をつけられない
no one can assign value.
それでも隣で生きていたい
Even so, I want to live by your side.
こんなに狭い星だから
Because this planet is so small,
肩でも組んでさ 歌いましょう
let's put our arms around each other and sing.
ずっと独りぼっちはもう最期
Being all alone is over now.
岩のように厚い雲を
Grasp the hand that secretly peeked out
こっそりと覗いた手を握って
from the clouds as thick as rocks,
引っ張り出して
and pull it out.
数多を照らす光は
The light that illuminates the many,
寂しい記憶も同じように
just like lonely memories,
数多全て照らし出すから
it illuminates everything.
照らそう... 負けないで進むだけ
Let's illuminate... just keep moving forward.
アマテラス テラス この手で
Amaterasu, illuminate with these hands,
触れて 笑って 踊りましょう
touch, laugh, and let's dance.
アマテラス テラス 気付かせて
Amaterasu, illuminate, make them realize.
あのね 君だって 歌えるよ
You know, even you can sing it.
世界中のどんな朝も
Any morning in the world,
8分前の光に満ちている
is filled with light from 8 minutes ago.
オキドキ 返事はいいけど
Okey-dokey, the answer is fine, but...
冗談なら笑えないよ
if it's a joke, I can't laugh.
渋滞 曖昧 どっちを向いてるの
Traffic jam, ambiguity, which way are you facing?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
Reached out my hand to the mirage.
微熱のような
Like a slight fever,
夢物語
a dream story.
そんな光はみんな無視してた
Everyone ignored such light.
喚く子供
Don't become
までいかないで
a screaming child.
真っ逆さま堕ちちゃったよ
I fell head over heels!
私を奪って
Steal me,
魅惑のダーリン
captivating Darling!
構わず Dance Dance Dance Just a Dance Just a Dance
Regardless, Dance Dance Dance, Just a Dance, Just a Dance.
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving my voice to the darkness...
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if I wake up, don't leave me.
Maybe Needy
正気じゃないのよ
I'm not in my right mind.
体温が忘れられない
I can't forget your warmth.
誰彼そんなじゃないから
It's not just anyone, you know.
独り占めして Euphoria
Monopolize me, Euphoria.
気にしてないような
Acting like you don't care,
言葉は装飾で
words are just decoration.
メイクのようには流せない
They can't be washed away like makeup.
360度 偽りだってさ
Even if 360 degrees of it is a lie,
隠しきれるような
as if you could hide it all.
私に構って
Pay attention to me.
嬉しいなんて Crazy Crazy Love
Saying you're happy, Crazy Crazy Love.
摩天楼から連れさらって
Take me away from this skyscraper.
君の存在は
Your existence...
私の深層心理を
...rewrites my deep psychology.
すり替えちゃうのよ 責任重大ね
It swaps everything out. You have a heavy responsibility.
過ぎ去ったネオン残像 Shooting Star
Passed neon afterimages, Shooting Star.
グライダーみたいに漂えば
If we drift like a glider,
幸も不幸もなかった
there was neither happiness nor unhappiness.
指先でまた君を探している
My fingertips are searching for you again.
その声を聴かせてよ
Let me hear that voice.
私に構って
Pay attention to me,
教えてよ恋の先を
tell me what lies beyond love!
拡がって収まんない Universe
Expanding uncontrollably, Universe.
君の存在は
Your existence...
私の将来までも
...stepped right into my future.
踏み込んだのよ 付き合ってよね
So go out with me, okay?
一切合切 Dance Dance Dance
Altogether, Dance Dance Dance.
We Are Dancing Reed
夢中になって絡み合った Zero Gravity
Entangled in obsession, Zero Gravity.
構わず Dance Dance Dance
Regardless, Dance Dance Dance.
Just a Dance Just a Dance
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving my voice to the darkness...
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if I wake up, don't leave me.
ひとつ！
One!
病める時も 健やかなる時も ずっと
In sickness and in health, always,
愛を歌い続けることを 堂々と誓います
I proudly swear to keep singing of love.
ふたつ！
Two!
トークがとか ダンスも もっと追求します
I will pursue my talks, dance, and more!
みっつ！
Three!
ずっと推してもらえるアイドルになってみせます
I'll prove I can become an idol you can support forever!
よっつめ！
Four!
不安な未来も 私が照らすんだ
I will illuminate even the anxious future.
それでも落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days I get depressed,
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔
I'm remembering everyone's smiles.
ここに宣言します
I declare it right here!
Are You Ready?
未完成の地図を輝きに変えて
Turning this unfinished map into radiance.
誰にも真似できない足跡を見ていて
Watch these footprints that no one else can imitate.
みんな！
Everyone!
走り出した願いは加速していくスピード
My wish has started running, speeding up.
目に映るものに戸惑うんなら
If you're bewildered by what you see in your eyes,
仮想世界だって私が見えてるでしょ
Even in a virtual world, you can see me, right?
キミだけに在る世界が正解
The world that exists only for you is the correct answer.
時々は泣き出したくもなるよ
Sometimes I even want to burst into tears.
だけどドキドキが胸締め付け止まらないから
But the excitement tightens my chest and won't stop.
大きくなってるんだってキミに届けたいよ
It's getting bigger, I want to reach you.
素顔になってたんだね未来も切り開くよ
I've become my true self, I'll open up the future too.
明けない夜だって光のない朝だって
Even a night that won't dawn, even a morning without light,
平気だよ一緒に笑いたいから
It's okay, because I want to laugh together with you.
綺麗になってるんだってチョビっと自信持って
I'm becoming beautiful, having a little confidence.
だから願ってたんだね此処で歌いたいと
That's why I was wishing to sing right here.
いつもよりもちょっと大きな声でもっと
With a voice a little louder than usual, more!
自分で決めてもいいんだよね… 正解！
It's okay to decide for yourself, right... Correct!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
声がちょっとちっちゃいかも！
Your voices might be a little quiet!
スポットライトをもうちょっと
Turn the spotlight up a little more,
当ててきて最高潮
Shine it on me and let's reach the climax.
不安も全部巻き込んで
Rolling up all my anxieties too,
上がるステージへ
Heading to the rising stage.
お淑やかに立って
Standing gracefully,
これが私のロックンロール
This is my Rock 'n' Roll.
キミだけに見せたいの… 正解！
I want to show it only to you... Correct!
みんな声出していけるかー！
Can everyone get their voices out?!
せーの！
One, two!
オイッス！
Oissu!
今日だけは 一緒に泣いてもいいよ
Just for today, it's okay to cry together.
だけど明日は 絶対明るい日と
But promise me that tomorrow,
約束だよして
will absolutely be a bright day!
Yeah!
落ち込んだって 立って
Even if I'm down, I'll stand up.
君に届けたいよ
I want to reach you.
スターになんて なって
Becoming a star,
未来を見に行こうよ
let's go see the future.
止まない雨だって
Even the rain that won't stop,
派手な向かい風だって
even the flashy headwind,
私たちを色濃く
they are the spices
彩るスパイスだから
that color us deeply.
綺麗になって なって
Becoming beautiful, beautiful,
ちょびっと自信持って
having a little bit of confidence.
目立たなくたって いいよ
It's okay even if you don't stand out.
君と一緒に
Because I want to sing
歌いたいから
together with you.
いつもよりも 誰よりも
More than usual, more than anyone,
大声で
with a loud voice,
君が大好き
I love you!
踏み出す魔法かけるよ
I'll cast a spell to help you step forward.
さあ
Come on!
Star! もっと! もっと!
Star! More! More!
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Start! Start! Start Dash!
まだまだススメ
Keep going, not yet done.
Step! Step! Step by Step!
倒れるまで
Until you fall.
忙しい視線
Busy gaze,
アンバランスシルエット
unbalanced silhouette.
見え隠れした そのEmotion
That emotion flickering in and out.
孤立された悪い悪い子はだあれ
Who is the isolated, bad, bad child?
ゆらゆら開始の合図
Swaying signal to start,
包まれ意地悪
enveloped in malice.
あの子の罠で踊りましょ
Let's dance in that girl's trap.
くすぶる火種着火 Fire!
Ignite the smoldering spark, Fire!
もっとちょうだい
Give me more.
君とStar Starになりたいだけなのに
I just want to be a Star Star with you,
揺れる心はラビリンス
but my swaying heart is a labyrinth.
君をStar Starにさせたいだけなのに
I just want to make you a Star Star,
すれ違う道
paths crossing,
ヒールはひとつでしょうか
is there only one heel?
もう気がついてる本当の正体から
I've already noticed the true identity,
逃げにはもうしないわ
so I won't run away anymore.
Star! Star! Star! Star!
Start! Start! Start Dash!
まだまだアソベ
Play more and more.
Run! Run! Runaway!
切れ長キャット
Slit-eyed cat,
飛び乗って
hop on.
痛い痛い覗きたい模様
Painful, painful, a pattern I want to peek at.
毒づくフリしたジョーカー
A Joker pretending to curse.
どうしようだからどうしよう
What should I do? So what should I do?
暗い暗い夜の中
In the dark, dark night.
踊る文字が私の世界に
Dancing letters in my world,
起こして
wake me up.
全てになって奏でよう
Become everything and play the music.
君とStar Starになりたいだけなのに
I just want to be a Star Star with you,
揺れる心はラビリンス
but my swaying heart is a labyrinth.
君をStar Starにさせたいだけなのに
I just want to make you a Star Star,
すれ違う道
paths crossing,
ヒールはひとつでしょうか
is there only one heel?
もう気がついてる運命出会うため
I've realized it's fate to meet you,
手と手合わせ踊りましょう
so let's join hands and dance.
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
要らない真実は
I'll make you forget
忘れさせてあげるから
the truths you don't need.
情熱の駆け引きに
If you softly face
そっと向いたら
the bargaining of passion.
君とStar Starに
With you, Star Star...
君とStar Starになりたいだけなのに
I just want to be a Star Star with you,
揺れる心はラビリンス
but my swaying heart is a labyrinth.
君をStar Starにさせたいだけなのに
I just want to make you a Star Star,
すれ違う道
paths crossing,
ヒールはひとつでしょうか
is there only one heel?
もう気がついてる本当の正体から
I've already noticed the true identity...
Oki doki 説明してよ
Oki doki, explain it to me.
冗談なら笑えないよ
If it's a joke, I can't laugh.
数回曖昧どっちが実情
Ambiguous several times, which is the truth?
蜃気楼にて翻弄された
Toyed with by a mirage.
微熱のような本能だったり
Like an instinct resembling a slight fever,
そんなん体験したことないし知ってた
I've never experienced that, and I knew it.
残像だってここにあるの
Even an afterimage is here.
まだいかないで　幻じゃないよ
Don't go yet, it's not an illusion.
私を奪って
Steal me away.
疑惑の残滓　確信犯
Residue of suspicion, a crime of conviction.
広がって　収まんない夕暮れ
Spreading out, an uncontrollable twilight.
不服の挙動は
This dissatisfied behavior is...
私の白昼夢
...my daydream.
だけどちょっと　背伸びしたいね
But I want to stretch a little.
逆らって　進んで　吸い込まれる
Resisting, advancing, getting sucked in.
私信じちゃって　空回り道
Believing in myself, going in circles.
構わず　ダンダンダン
Regardless, dun dun dun.
チャチャチャ
Cha cha cha.
声は逆光に預けたまま
Leaving my voice in the backlight.
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if you wake up, don't leave.
Baby baby 正気じゃないよ
Baby baby, I'm not in my right mind.
体力なんて残ってない
I have no stamina left.
Far away Far away
外野じゃないから
Because I'm not an outsider.
一目して恋煩いや
Lovesickness at first sight.
気にしてないような
Like I don't care.
素振り装飾で
With pretending and decoration.
迷宮のように罠が連鎖
Traps chained like a labyrinth.
残酷特注
Cruel custom order.
私にハマって
Fall for me.
妖艶な手口　Crazy Love
Bewitching trick, Crazy Love.
摩天楼が暮れたらへーい
When the skyscraper darkens, hey.
不滅の鼓動は
The immortal heartbeat is...
私の深層心理も
...my deep psychology too.
次過剰な誉め責任重大ね
Next, excessive praise, heavy responsibility.
次去ったネオン　残像シュレッダー
Neon that left next, afterimage shredder.
ゆらゆらみたいに漂えば
If I drift like swaying,
幸も不幸もなかった
There was neither happiness nor unhappiness.
指先でまた君を探している
Searching for you again with my fingertips.
その声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear that voice.
私に構って
Pay attention to me.
教えるよ恋の作法
I'll teach you the manners of love.
広がって　収まんない夢
Spreading out, an uncontrollable dream.
不明の正体は
The unknown identity is...
私の将来までも
...even my future.
覚悟がないならすぐヤメヤメ
If you're not prepared, quit immediately.
私を奪って
Steal me away.
疑惑の残滓　確信犯
Residue of suspicion, a crime of conviction.
構わず　ダンダンダン
Regardless, dun dun dun.
チャチャチャ
Cha cha cha.
声は逆光に預けたまま
Leaving my voice in the backlight.
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if you wake up, don't leave.
はーい！
Yesss!
みなさん新年あけましておめでとうございます！
Everyone, Happy New Year!
はーい！
Yesss!
盛り上がってますか？
Are you getting hyped?
みんなで協力して優しい気持ちでライブできてるかにょ？
Are we all cooperating and enjoying the live with kind feelings?
いいね　素晴らしいよ
Nice, that's wonderful.
みんな見えてるよ　今日はみんな青いんだね
I can see everyone. You're all blue today.
そっかあれか　あのTシャツ
I see, it's that. That T-shirt.
Tシャツが今着てくれてる人？
Who is wearing the T-shirt right now?
待って　当日券買ってくれた人っていますか？
Wait, is there anyone who bought a same-day ticket?
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
感動しちゃ...ありがとうございます本当に嬉しいです
I'm moved... thank you, really. I'm happy.
ということでね　やりましたあれをやりましょうか
So, we did that. Shall we do that?
えーそうです...ね
Umm... let's see...
遠くから来てくれた人！
People who came from far away!
そうだよね　飛行機とかで来てくれた人いたもんね
That's right, there were people who came by plane.
じゃあ　海外ニキニキ！
Then, overseas bros!
じゃあ...声は出さなくてもいい　あのぴょんぴょんやるだけでもいいよ
Then... you don't have to raise your voice. Just jumping is fine.
女の子！
Girls!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
前の方でぴょんぴょん飛んでるの見えたよ
I saw you jumping up and down in the front.
奥の方の子も見えてるよ
I can see the girls in the back too.
大声ありがとうございます
Thanks for the loud voices.
う〜ん、一回席！
Hmm, first floor seats!
イェ〜イ！
Yay!
じゃあまたペンライト遊びしちゃお。
Well then, let's play with penlights again.
左の人、緑！
People on the left, green!
右の人は、じゃあ...オレンジ！
People on the right, well then... orange!
じゃあ、真ん中は...青！
Then, the center... blue!
うわ〜綺麗だ！
Wow, it's beautiful!
みんな今回はね、こんな感じで、みんなも演出に参加しちゃうライブになっているよ。
Everyone, this time, it's a concert where you all get to participate in the production like this.
みんなで楽しんでいこうね！
Let's all have fun together!
今日はみんなも主役なんだ！
Today, everyone is a main character too!
は〜い！
Ye~s!
よし、よし、よし... よし！から！
Alright, alright, alright... Alright! Starting now!
夜はね、いっぱい動くと思って、
I thought I'd be moving a lot tonight,
ま、もう動いてるけど、昼から飲めばよかった。
well, I'm already moving, but I should've started drinking it at noon.
スポドリ一択！
Sports drink is the only choice!
ガッツリ！
Plenty!
今日、今年の目標みたいにムキムキになっていこうと思います。
Today, I think I'll get buff, just like my goal for this year.
頑張れ！
Do your best!
というわけで？
With that said?
じゃ〜ん、初めての人！
Ta-da! Any first-timers here?
あ、これ、拍手してくれてる、ありがとうございます。
Ah, you're clapping for me here, thank you.
一番最初のライブから全部来てるよって人いる？
Is there anyone who has come to every live since the very first one?
おお〜！ありがとうございます。
Ooh! Thank you very much.
というわけでね、みんなわかったね、はじめましての人も
So, you get it right? First-timers too,
いつもは「そらとも」じゃない人も
and those who aren't usually 'Soratomo' too,
そして昔から応援してる人、みんな集まって
and those who have supported me for a long time, gather together,
みんなが...既に「そらとも」だよ！
everyone... is already a 'Soratomo'!
みんな楽しく過ごしていこうね！
Let's all have a fun time!
というわけで...なんと...
So... actually...
YouTubeでの無料配信は...
the free stream on YouTube is...
まだ全部言ってないのに！
I haven't even said it all yet!
ここ... ここまで！
Here... ends here!
まだ来たばっかり！？
Just got here!?
まだ来たばっかりかと思うけど
I think you might have just got here, but
ま、続きは概要欄から...え、え、イェーイ...え、イェーイの人はどうしたの？
well, continue from the description... eh, eh, yay... eh, what's up with the 'yay' people?
ごめん！
Sorry!
あ、コメント会場、配信会場の人も楽しんでってね！
Ah, people in the comments and stream, have fun too!
わ〜い！
Ya~y!
それでは、もう一回飲んでから行くね。
Well then, I'll take one more drink before we go.
ちょっと水分も大事。
Hydration is important.
助かる！助かってくれてありがとう！
It helps! Thanks for saying it helps!
では、次の曲も楽しんで行ってね！
Well then, please enjoy the next song too!
まだほんのちょっとの涙流して
Shedding just a little bit more tears
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The introductory free stream ends here.
The free introductory stream ends here.